Oneida Community Collection
Oneida Community Collection
1811-1983
1850-1900
Oneida Community.
30.5 linear ft.
Community and personal records, biographical materials, and memorabilia pertaining to the Perfectionist community established by John Humphrey Noyes in Madison County, New York, its predecessor community in Putney, Vermont, and its branch communities in Wallingford, Connecticut and Brooklyn, New York, and the successor joint stock organization, Oneida Community, Ltd.
146332
Biographical History
The Oneida Community was a utopian commune founded by John Humphrey Noyes in 1848 in the town of Oneida in Madison County, New York. Noyes, born in Vermont in 1811, attended Dartmouth College, Andover Theological Seminary, and Yale Theological College and received his license to preach in 1834. He formed his first utopian community in 1836 in Putney, Vermont, practicing "complex marriage" in which every male was considered married to every female. In 1847 pending arrests for adultery spurred Noyes and several other Putney members to move to Oneida, New York, where they established the Oneida Community.
The Oneida community practiced communal property and possessions and believed in a form of Perfectionism -- Christ's Second Coming had occurred in the year 70 CE thus making it possible for them to bring about Christ's millennial kingdom and be free of sin and perfect in this world. (Noyes' declaration in 1834 that he himself was "Perfected" had resulted in the revocation of his license to preach.) To help members overcome character defects, all members -- including Noyes himself -- were subject to formal constructive criticism by committee, or by the community as a whole, a practice known as "mutual criticism."
As in Putney, the community rejected monogamy and practiced complex marriage. Noyes believed that sex had social and spiritual elements; members were expected to improve themselves via sexual relations with those who were their spiritual superiors. Noyes frequently suggested or encouraged particular pairings, and beginning in 1869 members who wished to have children could do so only with the partner selected for them by a committee based on personal, spiritual, and moral qualities (such controlled reproduction is known as "stirpiculture").
The community was self-supporting, primarily through the sale of animal traps, silk thread, and vegetables. (Silverware, for which the Oneida name would become well-known, was not produced until 1877.) Men and women were expected to work equally and had equal voice in community governance. At its height in 1878 the community had 306 members, but the community faltered the next year when Noyes attempt to pass on leadership of the community to his son, Theodore Noyes. By 1880 some members had left, many had embarked upon traditional marriages, and the community itself had been reorganized as a joint-stock company named Oneida Community Ltd. The animal trap, silk thread, and canned vegetable enterprises were all abandoned or sold off by 1916 but Oneida Community Ltd. became well-known for its silver and cutlery, production of which continued until 2005.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Oneida Community Collection contains community and personal records, biographical materials, and memorabilia pertaining to the Perfectionist community established by John Humphrey Noyes in Madison County, New York, its predecessor community in Putney, Vermont, and its branch communities in Wallingford, Connecticut and Brooklyn, New York, and the successor joint stock organization, Oneida Community, Ltd.
Of particular significance are the materials of William Alfred Hinds. William A. Hinds was a lifelong disciple of John Humphrey Noyes and lived for more than sixty years in the Oneida Community, and among the papers in this collection are Hinds' original research files for the revised editions of his American communities (Oneida, N.Y.: Office of the American Socialist, 1878). These files include his correspondence with individuals and communities, together with those documents which he received in connection with his questionnaire. This collection is an important and largely untapped resource available to those interested in the history of nineteenth-century communistic societies in America.
Architectural plans and renderings contains blueprints and pen-and-ink sketches of the Mansion House and Children's House.
Archives (George Wallingford Noyes) consists of photocopies of typed transcriptions of original documents, letters and other manuscripts relating to the Noyes family and the Oneida Community (1811-1880) compiled by George Wallingford Noyes. Original transcriptions in the possession of Mrs. Imogen Noyes Stone, Kenwood, New York.
Biographical material includes family registers, census schedules, membership lists, birth and death records, and other genealogical material.
Community records comprises more than twenty boxes of agreements, scrapbooks, indexes, inventories, sales books, record books, meeting minutes, requests for appropriations, and other community records. Included here are instances of "mutual criticism" for a number of members as well as a small number of photographs.
Manuscripts and personal papers contains nearly forty boxes of correspondence (also included are writings and other material for some individuals). Here also are located the papers (both correspondence and research) of Oneida resident and Utopian community scholar William Alfred Hinds (see above). More than 15 members of the Noyes family -- including George Wallingford Noyes, George Washington Noyes, Harriet Holton Noyes, John Humphrey Noyes, Pierrepont Noyes, and Theodore Richards Noyes -- are represented.
Oneida Community members for whom the collection contains significant amounts of material include Alfred Barron, George Cragin, Charles J. Guiteau, and Erastus Hamilton. Oneida Community materials also include documents relating to Beulah Hendee, James B. Herrick, Ann S. Bailey Hobart, Annie E. Kelly, Jessie Kinsley, Charlotte M. Leonard, Stephen R. Leonard, Charlotte A. Noyes Miller, George Noyes Miller, Helen Campbell Miller, Tirzah Miller, Seymour Nash, and Milford Newhouse. Materials also include documents relating to Harriet Noyes Skinner, John Langdon Skinner, Joseph John Skinner, Theodore H. Skinner, James W. Towner, Francis Wayland-Smith, Cornelia Worden, Harriet Maria Worden, Marquis de LaFayette Worden, and others.
Newspapers contains more than 50 local or northeastern United States alternative newspapers, including Banner of Light and Hull's Crucible (Boston); Daily Graphic and Worker (New York); Progressive communist (Kansas); Social-smasher (Berlin Heights, Ohio); Labor vindicator (New Martinsville, W.Va.); and Chariot of wisdom and love (Portland, Me.).
Maps, stored separately from the collection in the map case, contains maps of Oneida Community buildings and grounds as well as lands belonging to the Wallingford (Connecticut) community.
One item of Realia, a dress, completes the collection.
Other Formats Available
Some items from the collection have been scanned and are accessible through. Portions of the collection are also available on microfilm (see Microfilm 1951).
Arrangement of the Collection
Architectural plans and renderings are arranged chronologically. George Wallingford Noyes' archives are arranged chronologically. Biographical material is in no particular order. The Community records series is roughly but not consistently ordered with general material first, followed by socio-cultural material (dress, education, music, etc), business material (sales books, inventories, etc), and photographs; within these general topics material is roughly but not entirely chronological. Manuscripts and personal papers are arranged alphabetically by name of originator (sender, writer, or author). Newspapers are arranged alphabetically by name of the paper. Maps are arranged chronologically. Realis is in no particular order.
Related Material
See also the
P. Geoffrey Noyes Papers
. Selected books about the Oneida Community, and photographs of the Community buildings, members, and groups, have been scanned and are accessible in digital format via. The library also has numerous pamphlets, books, and other published material on the Oneida Community in its Rare Books holdings and in the general circulating collection; please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Activism and social reform; New York State; Religion and Philosophy; Barron, Alfred.; Cragin, George, 1808-1884.; Guiteau, Charles Julius, 1841-1882.; Hamilton, Erastus Hapgood, 1821-1894.; Hendee, Beulah Foster (Barron), 1847-1903.; Herrick, James Burton, 1837-1912.; Hinds, William Alfred, 1833-1910. American communities.; Hobart, Ann S. Bailey (Skinner), 1846-1908.; Kelly, Annie E. (Miller), 1852-1931.; Kinsley, Jessie Hatch, 1858-1938.; Leonard, Charlotte Miller, 1846-1928.; Leonard, Stephen Rose, 1820-1892.; Miller, Charlotte A. Noyes, 1819-1874.; Miller, George Noyes, 1845-1904.; Miller, Helen Campbell (Barron), 1847-1932.; Miller, Tirzah Crawford (Herrick), 1843-1902.; Nash, Seymour, 1814-1881.; Newhouse, Milford James, 1847-1926.; Noyes, George Wallingford.; Noyes, George Washington, 1822-1870.; Noyes, Harriet Ann Holton, 1808-1895.; Noyes, John Humphrey, 1811-1886.; Noyes, Pierrepont, 1870-; Noyes, Theodore Richards, 1841-1903.; Skinner, Harriet H. Noyes, 1817-1893.; Skinner, John Langdon, 1803-1889.; Skinner, Joseph John, 1842-1919.; Skinner, Theodore Hobart, 1878-1944.; Towner, James William, 1823-1913.; Wayland-Smith, Francis, 1841-1911.; Worden, Cornelia, 1847-1928.; Worden, Harriet Maria, 1840-1891.; Worden, Marquis de LaFayette, 1813-1891.; Oneida Community.; Oneida Community, ltd.; Oneida, ltd.; Putney Community (Putney, Vt.); Wallingford Community.; Oneida Community -- Archival resources.; Oneida Community -- Archives.; Christian communities -- United States.; Collective settlements -- United States.; Eugenics -- United States.; Perfection -- Religious aspects -- Christianity.; Utopias.; Architectural plans.; Autograph albums.; Birth registers.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Death registers.; Diaries.; Financial records.; Genealogies (histories); Inventories.; Ledgers (account books); Legal documents.; Maps (documents); Membership lists.; Minute books.; Periodicals.; Photographs.; Reminiscences.; Sales records.; Scrapbooks.; Sketches.; Stereographs.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Additional access restrictions on this material lifted as of January, 2007.
Acquisition Information
Majority of collection, gift of the Oneida Community Historical Committee.
One stereogram, purchased 2014.
Inventory
- Architectural plans and renderings
  - Mansion House south front rendering, pen-ink-water color wash; 34.5 x 52 cm. (original in OCMH Collection), 1850? (Map-case 73)
  - Mansion House east front rendering, pen-ink-water color wash; 22 x 63.5 cm. (original in OCMH Collection), 1850? (Map-case 73)
  - Mansion House west front rendering, pen-ink-water color wash; 23.5 x 61 cm. (original in OCMH Collection), 1850? (Map-case 73)
  - Set of 5 blueprints for 'New House,' prepared by L.W. Leeds & co., New York Basement; 1st floor; 2d floor; 3d floor; roof; 52.5 x 72 cm. (originals in OCMH Collection), 1877 (Map-case 73)
  - Foundation plan, 56 x 71.5 cm., and Section, 46.5 x 62.5 cm. (originals in OCMH Collection), 1877 (Map-case 73)
  - Mansion House south(?) elevation. By Mr. Whatley(?)
  - Children's House elevation rendering, undated (Map-case 73)
- Archives (George Wallingford Noyes)
  Restrictions removed January 2007.
  - 1811-1837 (Box 1)
  - 1838-1878 (Box 2)
  - 1879-1880 (Box 3)
- Biographical material
  - Genealogical data cards (Box 4)
  - Biographical data cards (incomplete) (Box 4)
  - Hilda Herrick Noyes, M.D. Collection (copy) (Box 5)
  - Genealogical information re: Oneida Community families compiled by Hilda Herrick Noyes copied with the permission of the present owner, Sylvia Noyes Paquette. (Box 5)
  - Census schedules
    - Federal census schedules (Madison Co., N.Y.), 1850; 1860,; 1870,; 1880 (Box 6)
    - New York state census schedules (Madison Co., Town of Lenox), 1855; 1865,; 1875 (Box 6)
  - Members of Putney Community and date of joining (Box 7)
  - Children of the Putney Community (Box 7)
  - Original list of O.C. members by Harriet A. Noyes (12 p.) (Box 7)
  - O.C. Family Register, Ja 1 1849; 16 p. typescript + 2 copies and alphabetical card file (Box 7)
  - Record of members (Box 7)
  - List of children brought here under the age of 16: alphabetical list, chronological list, 1848-1876 (Box 7)
  - O.C. & W.C. Register with typescript, 1862-1869 (Box 7)
  - O.C. & W.C. Census by M.L. Worden, 1869 (Box 7)
  - Members joining O.C. in 1849 (Box 7)
  - Signatures of members (Box 7)
  - Persons coming and going, 1865-1867 (Box 7)
  - Registers - Kept by John Abbott, 1871-1881 (Box 7)
  - Weight of O.C. babies, 1869-1877 (Box 7)
  - W.C. census, 1872-1876 (Box 7)
  - Marriages, 1879-1880 (Box 7)
  - Members of O.C. & W.C. under 5 years, Ja 1, 1880 (Box 7)
  - Community register, Ja 1, 1880 (Box 7)
  - O.C. register, undated (Box 7)
  - Record of births, undated (Box 7)
  - Record of deaths, undated (Box 7)
  - Names of seceders (Box 7)
  - Persons born in the O.C. (Box 7)
  - Hinds List of O.C. Members (Box 7)
  - Kenwood Interviews - Conducted by Maren Lockwood Carden, 1961; transcripts (copies) of 75 interviews processed to guarantee respondents' anonymity; Restrictions removed January 2007. (Box 8, 9)
  - Genealogical data sheets (photocopies), compiled by Sean Devlin and John Teeple (missing, 2007), 1980-1983 (Box 10)
- Community records
  - Declaration of the family of believers connected with J.H. Noyes at Putney (shorthand document with 7 signatures), 1846 Ag 18 (Box 11)
  - Synopsis of Community activity, 1848-1874 (Box 11)
  - O.C. Annals, 1847-1881 (Box 11)
  - Brooklyn School Journal (typescript), 1849-1850 (Box 11)
  - Wallingford Assocation Day Book & Journal, 1852-1853 (Box 11)
  - Daily Journal (mss. & typescript), 1863-1864 (Box 11)
  - Events, 1874 (Box 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1869-1879 (Box 12)
  - Travel to & from O.C. & W.C., 1878-1879 (Box 13)
  - Index of O.C. & Willow Place Talks, Reports and Journals with Cozicot Journal, 1875-1877 (Box 13)
  - Home talks indices, 4 volumes (Box 13)
  - General Index of Community Publications compiled by James B. Herrick, 1834-1869 [i.e. 1879] (Box 13)
  - Record book of stirpiculture, 1869; Stirpicultural data compiled by Hilda Herrick Noyes, M.D. (Box 14)
  - Anita Newcomb McGee Papers, 1869; copies; originals in Kinsey Institute (Box 14)
  - A.J. MacDonald Papers, 1868; collected, rearranged and commented upon by J.H.N. and T.R.N. (Box 14)
  - Visitor's Register, 1862-1868 (Box 15)
  - O.C. correspondence (copybook, p. 31-161), 1873-1876 (Box 15)
  - O.C. correspondence (copybook) (with Minutes of the session of the Commission appointed July 17, 1880), 1876-1884 (Box 15)
  - Personal record - Description of Newman A. Brown by C. W. Underwood, 1865 (Box 16)
  - Mutual Criticism, criticisms of the following individuals: L.F. Dunn, G.N. Miller, J.B. Herrick, M.L. Prindle, T.C. Miller, Mr. Yoder, E. Newhouse, W. Mills, L. Hobart, R. Burnham, H. Allen, M.L. Worden (Box 16)
  - Herbarium, misc. correspondence between Hope E. Allen and H.D. House (Box 16)
  - Wallingford Water Power (Box 16)
  - Cozicot (Short Beach, Conn.) (Box 16)
  - Wallingford Tornado, 1878 (Box 16)
  - Watchmen's duties, undated (Box 16)
  - Minutes of seance, undated (Box 16)
  - Menus, 1877 (Box 16)
  - Buildings (Box 16)
  - Inquiries to O.C., 1907-1912 (Box 16)
  - Entertainment
    - Joseph and his brethren, 1858 (Box 17)
    - Broadsides (Box 17)
    - Trip of O.C. Brass Band to Cazenovia Lake, 1862 (Box 17)
  - Dress (Box 17)
  - Education (Box 17)
  - Music (Box 17)
  - Art: Community portraits (Box 17)
  - Library record book (501 p.) (Oversize 1)
  - Library catalogue (with entries to 1879) (Box 18)
  - Library Index and Record: Wallingford Library (with H.A. Noyes notation on cover and with records to 1875) (Box 18)
  - List of medical books transferred to New York State Library (Box 18)
  - Statement of the property of the Three Associations, 1855 (Box 19)
  - Receipts and settlements with seceders, 1855-1892 (Box 19)
  - Release of property by the members... to J.H. Noyes, 1865 (Ap 19) (Box 19)
  - Inventories of property brought to O.C. by new members, 1865-1879 (Box 19)
  - Covenant of the Oneida Community (copy), 1875 Ag 18 (Box 19)
  - O.C. Journal, 1880 (Ja-N) (Box 19)
  - Original notes of the Commission, 1880 (Jl-S) (Box 19)
  - Record of the proceedings of the Commission, 1880 (Jl-N) (Box 19)
  - Deposits by present members, 1880 (Ag) (Oversize 1)
  - Deposits by members on joining, 1880 (Ag 1) (Box 20)
  - Agreement to divide & reorganize (signed copy), 1880 (S 1) (Box 20)
  - Agreement to divide & reorganize (3 mss., typescript), 1880 (S-N) (Box 20)
  - Division of assets: worksheets illustrating various plans, 1880 (Oversize 1)
  - "Compromise plan", 1880 (S 15) (Box 20)
  - Division sheet, 1880 (O 30) (Box 20)
  - Agreement to divide & reorganize:, 1880 (Box 20)
  - Right to inhabit dwellings (Box 20)
  - Receipt for shares in Oneida Community Ltd. and release of Oneida Community from future liability, 1880 N 3 (Box 20)
  - Agreement as to control of stock, 1880 N 10 (Box 20)
  - Mutual release, 1880 N 10 (Box 20)
  - Settlement of O.C. with members, 1880 N 10-30 (Box 20)
  - Ledger showing settlement, 1880 N-D (Box 20)
  - Furniture & bedding assigned to members, 1880 D (Box 20)
  - Property put into O.C. by each member, 1880 (Box 20)
  - Financial arrangements establishing O.C.L., 1880-1884 (Box 20)
  - Clippings, various dates (Box 20)
  - A business history of Oneida Community Ltd. by H.V. Noyes and S.R. Leonard (unpublished typescript) (Box 21)
  - Animal Trap Co. of America by Richard G. Woolworth, 1951 (Box 21)
  - Leonard, Stephen R. Trap Book (copy; original owned by Mrs. A. Beagle) (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous drafts by S.R. Leonard of business history (Box 21.1)
  - Putney Store ledger, 1842-1848 (Box 22)
  - Putney Store ledger, 1846 (Box 22)
  - Business Board Minute Book, 1863-1867 (Box 23)
  - Business Board Minute Book, 1867-1875 (Box 23)
  - Business Board Minute Book, 1875-1880 (Box 23)
  - Finance Committee Minute Book, 1875-1877 (Box 23)
  - Report on 'Private speculation' (mss. & typescript), published in quadrangle, pp. 6-8., Ag. 1930 (Box 24)
  - Property register of the O.C., 1859 (Box 24)
  - Account book, 1862-1863 (Box 24)
  - Agricultural works sales book, 1865-1871 (Box 24)
  - General office letter book, 1867-1869 (Box 24)
  - Estimates & memoranda on manufacturing [George Cragin), 1869-1871 (Box 24)
  - Fruit sales and profits, 1872-1882 (Box 24)
  - Requests for appropriations for projects, 1873 (Box 25)
  - Requests for appropriations for projects, 1874 (Box 25)
  - Special appropriations (pp. 10-85), 1874 (Box 25)
  - Distribution of work, 1874-1875 (Box 25)
  - Wallingford Community cash book, 1876-1881 (Box 25)
  - Weekly summary of Community labor, 1877 (Box 25)
  - Requests for appropriations for projects, 1877 (Box 25)
  - Requests for appropriations for projects, 1878 (Box 25)
  - Distribution of work, 1878-1879 (Box 25)
  - Stereotype plate, 1850 (Oversize 1)
  - Noyes, Harriet A. History of the printing business of O.C. (original in H.A. Noyes file), typescript, 2 copies (Box 26)
  - 'Circular' subscription books, 1863-1866; 4 volumes (Box 26)
  - Notices of 'Trapper's Guide', 1865 (Box 26)
  - Printing Department Account Book (copy), 1865-1868 (Box 26)
  - Wallingford Printing Company job book, 1875-1877 (Oversize 2)
  - Wallingford Printing Co. Minute Book, 1871-1878 (Box 26)
  - 'American Socialist' copybook (p. 5-230), 1876-1881 (Box 27)
  - Letters to 'Circular' editor, various dates (Box 27)
  - American Socialist subscription book (blank), 1876- (Box 27)
  - Tableware department - misc. price lists (Box 28)
  - Robert Wallace vs. J.H. Noyes, 1882
    - Brief for complainant (Box 28)
    - Complainant's pleadings & proofs (Box 28)
    - Defendants answer & evidence (Box 28)
  - Fruit Department sales/letter book, 1865-1866 (Box 29)
  - Fruit Department sales book, 1873-1874 (Box 29)
  - Fruit Department sales book, 1874-1877 (Box 29)
  - Fruit Department sales book, 1877-1879 (Box 30)
  - Fruit Department sales book, 1879-1880 (Box 30)
  - Inventories, 1858-1864 (Box 31)
  - Inventories, 1865-1867 (Box 31)
  - Inventories, 1868-1871 (Box 32)
  - Inventory, 1872 (Box 32)
  - Inventories, 1873-1876 (Box 33)
  - Inventory, 1877 (Box 34)
  - Inventories, 1878-1879 (Box 34)
  - Inventories, 1880-1882 (Box 35)
  - Inventory, 1882 (Box 36)
  - Inventory, 1883 (Box 36)
  - Photographs (stereograms)
    - Mansion House front portico, 1870 (Box 37)
      This item purchased by, 2014.
    - 'Views of the Oneida Community' - Photographer: Ranger & Austin, Syracuse, 1871-1872(?); 28 items (Box 37)
    - [no year] 'Views of the Oneida Community Domain', 4 items (Box 37)
    - [no year] 'Photographic views of the Oneida Community' - Photographer: D.E. Smith, 9 items (Box 37)
    - [no year] 'View of the railroad trestle on the O.C. domain' (Box 37)
    - [no year] Untitled views - Photographer: Richardson & Clark, Oneida, 3 items (Box 37)
    - [no year] Untitled views - Photographer: A.T. Richardson, Oneida, 4 items (Box 37)
    - [no year] Untitled, unsigned views, 12 items (Box 37)
    - [no year] Bag Bee (Box 37)
    - [no year] Oneida Community, -- Group No. 1 W.F. Richardson, Oneida (Box 37)
    - John Humphrey Noyes daguerreotype, circa 1840 (Box 37A)
- Manuscripts and personal papers
  - Abbott, Jane L., 1904; 1906 (Box 38)
    1904 Mr 28 to William A. Hinds
    1906 My 6 to William A. Hinds
  - Abbott, John, 1850; 1875 (Box 38)
    1850 D 2 to Marcus L. Worden
    1875 Mr 28 to Tirzah C. Miller
  - Achilli, Giacinto (Box 38)
    Biographical materials
    Dealings with the Inquisition (London, 1851)
  - Ackley, Alice, 1856-1877 (Box 38)
    1856 O 31 to Marcus L. Worden
    1871 Mr 12 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    1877 F 10 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    [no year] Ap 28 to Harriet N. Olds
  - Ackley, Joseph C., 1847-1892 (Box 38)
    1847 O 22 to H. Cook
    1876 D 28 to Julia C. Ackley (copy)
    1881 F Mr, Ap Oneida Community Ltd. statements
    1888 F 10 to H.G. Allen
    N 4 to Corinna (copy)
    1890 F 15 Last Will and Testament
    1891 N 12 Record of Births/Deaths of ancestors and also of brothers & sisters and my own family with excerpts from unpublished? Home talks by John Humphrey Noyes
    1892 N 26 to Corinna (copy) undated to James B. Herrick
    Autobiography (copy)
  - Ackley, Julia Carrier, 1870-1895 (Box 38)
    1870 Ap 7 to Harriet N. Olds
    1877 Mr 19 to Harriet N. Olds
    1878 Jl 8 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1880 My 21 to Tirzah C. Miller
    N 1 to Tirzah C. Miller
    N 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Diaries:
    1853-54
    1856-60; 1886-88; 1890-92
    1876-78
    1876-77 (typescript)
    1878-81
    1887
    1893-94
    1894
    1895
    Writings: Mrs. A.'s Story (typescript)
  - Aiken, Eliza, 1879-1886 (Box 38)
    1879 Je 12 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ag 1 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ag 2 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ag 3 to Mary Louise Prindle
    5 4 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1880 Jl 27 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Ag to Tirzah C. Miller
    1886 O 7 to M. K. Barron D
    26 to M. K. Barron D
    31 to M. K. Barron
    [no year] Ap 20 to Mary Louise Prindle
    undated Mon. to Mary Louise Prindle
  - Aiken, Laura, 1859 (Box 38)
    My 22 to Marcus L. Worden